OK so we'll start from the simplest thing.
好的，所以我们将从最简单的事情开始。
How we talk about something in the past when something happened before it's done it's finished and we
我们如何谈论过去的事情 当事情发生在它完成之前它已经完成并且我们
don't really care about maybe the details of it happening before.
并不真正关心它之前发生的细节。
Another thing that happened.
发生的另一件事。
There's just something that's that's finished.
只是有些事情已经完成了。
We use what we call the simple past.
我们使用我们所谓的简单过去时。
And when we do this we need to change verbs into the past tense.
当我们这样做时，我们需要将动词变为过去时。
The only thing that's really hard about this is knowing that sometimes you add e d to words and sometimes
唯一真正困难的是知道有时你会在单词中添加 d 有时
you don't.
你没有。
And the best way to learn that is to just see many examples and get the feeling for it.
学习这一点的最好方法就是看很多例子并感受它。
So make sure when you're watching movies or reading you pay attention to the different ways that verbs
因此，请确保在看电影或阅读时注意动词的不同方式
are changed into the past tense.
都变成过去时了。
But anyway just a couple of very simple examples I think you probably already know this.
但无论如何，只是几个非常简单的例子，我想你可能已经知道了。
So we'll we'll keep it really really basic.
所以我们将保持它非常非常基本。
OK.
好的。
Actually you know what's the hardest part about this.
其实你知道这件事最难的部分是什么。
The hardest part I find with students who are learning English is remembering to do it.
我发现在学习英语的学生中最难的部分是记住去做。
For example maybe a student will say I run to the store I run to the store.
例如，也许一个学生会说我跑到商店我跑到商店。
And then if I say you said I run to the store then the student will say I said run to the store I should
然后如果我说你说我跑到商店然后学生会说我说我应该跑到商店
have said I ran to the store and then I'll say But you didn't you said I run to the store and they go
已经说过我跑到商店然后我会说但是你没有说我跑到商店然后他们走了
Oh.
哦。
So actually the tough part for many learners of English is not knowing you know that ran that ran is
所以实际上，对于许多英语学习者来说，最困难的部分是不知道你知道跑那跑是
the past tense for run and you probably know that.
run 的过去式，你可能知道。
But when you're speaking you're thinking about a lot of different things at the same time.
但是当你说话的时候，你会同时考虑很多不同的事情。
Which words should I use.
我应该使用哪些词。
What things should be in the past and what things should not.
什么事情应该过去，什么事情不应该过去。
How do I fit this whole sentence together.
我如何将整个句子组合在一起。
What am I going to talk about next.
接下来我要讲什么。
And because you have so many things going on at the same time it's easy to make a mistake.
而且因为你同时有很多事情要做，所以很容易犯错误。
So when you're speaking you have to be very careful you have to pay attention to what's coming out of
所以当你说话的时候，你必须非常小心，你必须注意说话的内容
your mouth.
你的嘴。
If to hear yourself and try to catch it and correct it right away.
如果听到自己的声音并尝试抓住它并立即纠正它。
And if you do that you can get into the habit of saying it the right way.
如果你这样做了，你就会养成正确表达的习惯。
If you're always correcting yourself after you say it because you said the wrong thing and you heard
如果你总是在说错话后纠正自己，因为你说错了，你听到了
yourself say it that's the first step then change it corrected.
你自己说这是第一步然后改变它更正。
Then you can start doing it in your head.
然后你就可以开始在你的脑海里做这件事了。
You can start doing it in your head then you're OK.
你可以开始在你的脑海里做，然后你就可以了。
You're expressing it correctly.
你正确地表达了它。
OK.
好的。
So I really pay attention.
所以我真的很关注。
Slow down when you're speaking not worry about speaking very quickly.
说话时放慢速度，不要担心说得太快。
You don't have to speak quickly speak slowly and listen be aware of yourself awareness awareness.
你不必说得快说得慢，听得懂自己的觉知。
Today is the day where I'm breaking words and half.
今天是我断断续续的一天。
Awareness is the key to changing habits.
意识是改变习惯的关键。
And one of the one of the worst speaking habits for English learners is not changing very simple verbs
英语学习者最糟糕的口语习惯之一就是不改变非常简单的动词
into the past tense.
变成过去式。
So awareness is the key to changing speaking habits.
所以意识是改变说话习惯的关键。
So remember that for everything but especially for this lesson.
所以请记住这一点，尤其是本课。
OK.
好的。
So some examples.
所以一些例子。
Take walk.
走走。
OK.
好的。
Walk is E.D..
Walk 是 E.D.
This is a regular one so to make walk the past tense we just add E.D..
这是一个常规的，所以为了让 walk 成为过去式，我们只需添加 E.D.。
No problem.
没问题。
Very easy.
很容易。
I it's super easy I walked I walked to work yesterday.
我是超级容易我走路我昨天走路去上班。
Piece of cake.
小菜一碟。
That means something is very easy right.
这意味着有些事情很容易对。
It's a piece of cake.
很简单的。
I walked to work yesterday.
我昨天走路去上班。
Change that to E.D. and we're fine.
将其更改为 E.D.我们很好。
No problem.
没问题。
OK.
好的。
How about find is find find it.
怎么样find是find找到它。
No it's not.
不，这不对。
So this one is not regular E.D..
所以这个不是普通的 E.D.。
This is what we would call irregular irregular.
这就是我们所说的不规则不规则。
So this would be found.
所以会找到这个。
All right.
好的。
I found this in my car.
我在我的车里发现了这个。
Pretty simple pretty simple.
很简单很简单。
It's the same as saying I find this in my car.
这就像说我在我的车里找到这个一样。
The only difference is that we've changed into the past tense.
唯一的区别是我们已经变成了过去时。
We've changed the verb into the past tense.
我们把动词改成了过去时。
Everything else is the same.
其他一切都是一样的。
Doesn't need to be changed.
不需要改变。
Pretty pretty simple.
相当简单。
OK let's just do let's just do one more really really quick example.
好吧，让我们再做一个非常非常快速的例子。
Wait wait.
等等。
All right.
好的。
That's a regular one.
这是一个常规的。
That's E.D..
那是E.D.
So but this one pronunciation we don't say wait or something like that we say waited.
所以，但是这个发音我们不说等待或类似的东西，我们说等待。
It's very clearly pronounced as ID because of the T sound.
由于 T 音，它非常清楚地发音为 ID。
If you don't know how to use the E.D. pronunciation then you need to watch one of my other courses about
如果您不知道如何使用 E.D.发音然后你需要看我的其他课程之一
pronunciation to to know how to say that correctly.
发音要知道如何正确地说。
And other E.D. sounds.
和其他 E.D.声音。
Anyway let's look at the example then I waited and a lot of people will pronounce this as waited waited.
无论如何，让我们看一下这个例子，然后我等待，很多人会将此发音为waited waited。
It's almost a d sound waited I waited I waited all morning for the call I waited all morning I waited
几乎是 d 的声音 等待 我等了 整个上午都在等待电话 我等了整个上午 我等了
all morning for the call.
整个上午的电话。
Pretty simple.
很简单。
OK.
好的。
Why is it simple past.
为什么简单过去。
Why is it this one why is it waited instead of another one because it's finished.
为什么是这个，为什么它等待而不是另一个，因为它已经完成了。
It's a thing that happened.
这是发生的事情。
Now it's done.
现在它完成了。
We don't have to worry about its relationship to other things that happened and so we just use this
我们不必担心它与发生的其他事情的关系，所以我们只使用它
one.
一。
It's pretty simple OK.
这很简单。
Now I hope you have a pretty clear idea about how to use the simple past.
现在我希望你对如何使用简单过去有一个非常清晰的想法。
It's really just a warm up.
这真的只是一个热身。
Let's get into some of the more complicated stuff.
让我们进入一些更复杂的东西。
Some of the more difficult and juicy bits of past tense.
过去时的一些更困难和多汁的部分。
This is where it hopefully gets a little bit more interesting.
这就是它希望变得更有趣的地方。
So let's let's get started on that.
所以让我们开始吧。